I need help!
我需要帮助！
I have to fix a leaking pipe in my bathroom but I’m not sure where to begin.
我得修理浴室里漏水的的水管，但我不确定从哪里开始。
I know I lack the necessary DIY skills, but luckily there are numerous books and online videos that will hopefully give me the information I need.
我知道我缺乏必要的自己动手的技能，但幸运的是，有许多的书籍和在线视频，有望给我提供我需要的信息。
Publications that help us to help ourselves are nothing new, but the range of them is increasing with advice being given far beyond practical tasks around the house.
帮助我们自助的出版物并不是什么新鲜事，但这类出版物的范围在不断扩大，所提供的建议远远超出了家庭的实用任务。
Bookshops these days are full of titles which claim to boost your self-confidence, your wealth, your love life or your career.
如今的书店里摆满了各种书籍，这些书籍的标题声称可以增强你的自信心、增加你的财富、改善你的爱情生活或提升你的职业发展。
Some claim to improve your life within seven days!
有些书甚至声称能在七天内改善你的生活！
It‘s big business and it’s thought that the self-help industry is worth $10bn in the US alone.
这可是个大生意，据说仅在美国，自助类产业的价值就高达100亿美元。
The first self-help book called ‘How to Win Friends and Influence People‘ was published in 1936, and has since sold 30 million copies and is still popular now.
第一本自助书籍《如何赢得朋友和影响他人》于1936年出版，从那以后已经售出了3000万册，并且至今仍然很受欢迎。
It includes guidance on how to make people like you and how to make your life happier.
这本书包括了如何让别人喜欢你以及如何让你的生活更幸福的指导。
It might seem strange to think that we need a book to tell us how to live our lives but self-help books remain a go-to remedy for those of us looking for enlightenment.
想到我们需要一本书来告诉我们如何生活，这可能看起来很奇怪，但对于我们这些寻求启迪的人来说，自助书籍仍然是一种首选的解决办法。
There are, of course, trends in what we need help with.
当然，在我们需要帮助的事情上也存在一些趋势。
Emma Marshall, who works at British bookshop Waterstones, says “at the moment we’re in the tidying up, getting rid of things trend... I think the trend right now is about slowing down in your life.”
在英国水石书店工作的艾玛·马歇尔说：“目前我们正处于整理、清理东西的潮流中......我认为现在的潮流是让你的生活慢下来。”
It seems there is always something we need help with, and reading about it can be very therapeutic - it makes us feel good, even if we don‘t do anything about it.
似乎总是有一些我们需要帮助的事情，而且阅读相关内容可能是非常有疗效的——它让我们感觉良好，即使我们对此什么也不做。
Of course, the internet has become the place to go to for salvation.
当然，互联网已经成为寻求救赎的地方。
We’ve got used to searching for solutions online, and now these solutions even include how to fix or improve our lives.
我们已经习惯了在网上搜索解决方案，现在这些解决方案甚至包括如何修复或改善我们的生活。
Interestingly, psychologist Caroline Beaton, says people called ‘millennials‘ are self-critical — they are aware of their own faults — which also means they’re more likely to spend time and money on self-help.
有趣的是，心理学家卡罗琳·比顿说，被称为“千禧一代”的人很擅于自我批评——他们知道自己的缺点——这也意味着他们更有可能在自助方面花费时间和金钱。
There‘s also a theory that the self-help industry does well during a recession — people are perhaps even more likely to reach for self-help to improve their situation.
还有一种理论认为，自助类产业在经济衰退期间表现良好——人们可能更倾向于寻求自助来改善自己的处境。
Whatever the reason for the continued interest in self-help, it’s good to know help is at hand when we need it.
无论人们对自助持续感兴趣的原因是什么，知道在我们需要帮助的时候，帮助就在身边是件好事。
The alternative to finding a happier life is just to come to terms with yourself as you are - I know, I read about it in a book!
除了寻找更幸福的生活之外，另一种选择就是接受真实的自己——我知道，我在一本书里读到过！
Do you believe in self-help books?
你相信自助书籍吗？